[{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980377460,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"36","question":"Describe a time you felt most full of joy.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":63270,"timeElapsed":139317},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980402302,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"36","question":"Describe a time you felt most full of joy.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":24831,"timeElapsed":164158},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980451861,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"36","question":"Describe a time you felt most full of joy.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":49554,"timeElapsed":213717},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980460218,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"36","question":"Describe a time you felt most full of joy.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":8352,"timeElapsed":222074},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980468027,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"36","question":"Describe a time you felt most full of joy.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":7804,"timeElapsed":229883},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980475916,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"36","question":"Describe a time you felt most full of joy.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":7887,"timeElapsed":237773},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980481220,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"36","question":"Describe a time you felt most full of joy.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":5301,"timeElapsed":243076},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980496925,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"36","question":"Describe a time you felt most full of joy.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":15697,"timeElapsed":258782},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980503303,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"36","question":"Describe a time you felt most full of joy.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":6369,"timeElapsed":265159},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980512712,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"208","question":"Do you consider yourself more of a “cat person” or a “dog person”? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":7325,"timeElapsed":274569},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980518580,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"208","question":"Do you consider yourself more of a “cat person” or a “dog person”? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":5862,"timeElapsed":280437},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980528627,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"208","question":"Do you consider yourself more of a “cat person” or a “dog person”? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":10040,"timeElapsed":290483},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980533284,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"208","question":"Do you consider yourself more of a “cat person” or a “dog person”? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":4653,"timeElapsed":295140},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980537130,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"208","question":"Do you consider yourself more of a “cat person” or a “dog person”? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":3843,"timeElapsed":298987},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980541798,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Do you consider yourself more of a “cat person” or a “dog person”? Why?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4665,"timeElapsed":303655},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980545924,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"208","question":"Do you consider yourself more of a “cat person” or a “dog person”? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4120,"timeElapsed":307781},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980548949,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"208","question":"Do you consider yourself more of a “cat person” or a “dog person”? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3020,"timeElapsed":310806},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980555035,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"208","question":"Do you consider yourself more of a “cat person” or a “dog person”? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":6082,"timeElapsed":316892},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980562252,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"208","question":"Do you consider yourself more of a “cat person” or a “dog person”? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":7212,"timeElapsed":324109},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980581698,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"131","question":"Do you find dancing embarrassing? Why or why not? Describe the last time you danced.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":17711,"timeElapsed":343555},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980591774,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"131","question":"Do you find dancing embarrassing? Why or why not? Describe the last time you danced.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":10070,"timeElapsed":353631},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980595995,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"131","question":"Do you find dancing embarrassing? Why or why not? Describe the last time you danced.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":4217,"timeElapsed":357852},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980603884,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"131","question":"Do you find dancing embarrassing? Why or why not? Describe the last time you danced.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":7884,"timeElapsed":365741},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980609780,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"131","question":"Do you find dancing embarrassing? Why or why not? Describe the last time you danced.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":5893,"timeElapsed":371636},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980614762,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"131","question":"Do you find dancing embarrassing? Why or why not? Describe the last time you danced.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":4979,"timeElapsed":376619},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980619259,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"131","question":"Do you find dancing embarrassing? Why or why not? Describe the last time you danced.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4495,"timeElapsed":381116},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980625622,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"131","question":"Do you find dancing embarrassing? Why or why not? Describe the last time you danced.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":6355,"timeElapsed":387477},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980631836,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"131","question":"Do you find dancing embarrassing? Why or why not? Describe the last time you danced.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":6209,"timeElapsed":393692},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980643868,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"195","question":"Did you play any sports growing up? If multiple, which was your favorite? Do you still play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":10259,"timeElapsed":405725},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980647851,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"195","question":"Did you play any sports growing up? If multiple, which was your favorite? Do you still play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":3975,"timeElapsed":409708},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980671413,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"195","question":"Did you play any sports growing up? If multiple, which was your favorite? Do you still play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":23560,"timeElapsed":433269},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980682395,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"195","question":"Did you play any sports growing up? If multiple, which was your favorite? Do you still play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":10978,"timeElapsed":444252},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980686628,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"195","question":"Did you play any sports growing up? If multiple, which was your favorite? Do you still play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":4230,"timeElapsed":448485},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980692547,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"195","question":"Did you play any sports growing up? If multiple, which was your favorite? Do you still play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":5914,"timeElapsed":454404},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980695533,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"195","question":"Did you play any sports growing up? If multiple, which was your favorite? Do you still play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2982,"timeElapsed":457390},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980701740,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"195","question":"Did you play any sports growing up? If multiple, which was your favorite? Do you still play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":6201,"timeElapsed":463597},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980705060,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"195","question":"Did you play any sports growing up? If multiple, which was your favorite? Do you still play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":3316,"timeElapsed":466917},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980715717,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":6405,"timeElapsed":477574},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980722949,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":7224,"timeElapsed":484805},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980728435,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5482,"timeElapsed":490292},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980731143,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":2703,"timeElapsed":493000},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980734938,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":3793,"timeElapsed":496795},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980740752,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":5807,"timeElapsed":502608},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980746612,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5857,"timeElapsed":508469},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980753347,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":6730,"timeElapsed":515204},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980757019,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":3661,"timeElapsed":518876},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980767884,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":8242,"timeElapsed":529740},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980775684,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":7796,"timeElapsed":537540},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980784588,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":8896,"timeElapsed":546445},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980789947,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":5353,"timeElapsed":551804},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980796508,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":6556,"timeElapsed":558365},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980800715,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":4201,"timeElapsed":562572},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980806172,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":5453,"timeElapsed":568029},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980818770,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":12593,"timeElapsed":580627},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980822100,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":3328,"timeElapsed":583957},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980831484,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"48","question":"Do you believe in fate or destiny? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":7260,"timeElapsed":593341},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980836452,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"48","question":"Do you believe in fate or destiny? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":4965,"timeElapsed":598309},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980846460,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"48","question":"Do you believe in fate or destiny? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":10003,"timeElapsed":608317},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980849715,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"48","question":"Do you believe in fate or destiny? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":3250,"timeElapsed":611571},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980855452,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"48","question":"Do you believe in fate or destiny? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":5733,"timeElapsed":617309},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980859813,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"48","question":"Do you believe in fate or destiny? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":4357,"timeElapsed":621670},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980864014,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"48","question":"Do you believe in fate or destiny? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":4195,"timeElapsed":625871},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980871164,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"48","question":"Do you believe in fate or destiny? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":7146,"timeElapsed":633021},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980873372,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"48","question":"Do you believe in fate or destiny? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":2206,"timeElapsed":635229},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980882034,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":7149,"timeElapsed":643891},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980886766,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":4730,"timeElapsed":648623},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980892859,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":6088,"timeElapsed":654716},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980897252,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":4390,"timeElapsed":659109},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980901869,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":4612,"timeElapsed":663725},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980909861,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":7987,"timeElapsed":671717},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980913074,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3209,"timeElapsed":674931},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980917317,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4241,"timeElapsed":679174},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980921780,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4455,"timeElapsed":683637},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980937043,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"134","question":"When was the last time you walked for more than an hour? Describe where you went and what you saw.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":13532,"timeElapsed":698900},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980940756,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"134","question":"When was the last time you walked for more than an hour? Describe where you went and what you saw.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":3709,"timeElapsed":702613},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980950694,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"134","question":"When was the last time you walked for more than an hour? Describe where you went and what you saw.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":9934,"timeElapsed":712550},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980953114,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"134","question":"When was the last time you walked for more than an hour? Describe where you went and what you saw.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":2415,"timeElapsed":714971},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980957957,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"When was the last time you walked for more than an hour? Describe where you went and what you saw.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4837,"timeElapsed":719813},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980962204,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"134","question":"When was the last time you walked for more than an hour? Describe where you went and what you saw.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":4243,"timeElapsed":724061},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980967500,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"134","question":"When was the last time you walked for more than an hour? Describe where you went and what you saw.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5289,"timeElapsed":729357},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980970788,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"134","question":"When was the last time you walked for more than an hour? Describe where you went and what you saw.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3283,"timeElapsed":732644},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980978866,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"134","question":"When was the last time you walked for more than an hour? Describe where you went and what you saw.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":8073,"timeElapsed":740723},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980981332,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"134","question":"When was the last time you walked for more than an hour? Describe where you went and what you saw.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":2464,"timeElapsed":743189},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980995020,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":10026,"timeElapsed":756877},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980997667,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2642,"timeElapsed":759524},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981002955,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":5284,"timeElapsed":764812},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981005396,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2437,"timeElapsed":767253},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981008940,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":3538,"timeElapsed":770797},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981012558,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":3611,"timeElapsed":774414},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981016957,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":4391,"timeElapsed":778814},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981020235,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":3272,"timeElapsed":782092},{"subjectID":"ua8c4oz86m","prolificID":"611341c34be95409850e4341","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b236d1ce0ce826c688b1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981022606,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2367,"timeElapsed":784461}]